Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Residential Colleges
    - Jonathan Edwards College - Reunion, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 76)
    - Master Appointments - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 77)
    - Master Reappointment and Search, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 78)
    - Master Searches - Candidates, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 79)
    - Morse College - Master Appointment - Panter-Brick, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 80)
    - Morse College - Master Search - Announcements, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 81)
    - New Colleges - Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 25, Folder 82)
    - New Colleges - Groundbreaking Event, 2015 April 16 (Box 25, Folder 83)
    - New Colleges - Johnson Call, 2013 September 10 (Box 25, Folder 84)
    - New Colleges - Naming Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 85)
    - Pierson College - Master Appointment - Davis, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 86)
    - President's Dinner for College Masters - Photograph, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 87)
    - Saybrook College - Master Appointment - Hudak, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 88)
    - Saybrook College -Master Appointment - Near, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 89)
    - Saybrook College - Master Review Committee, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 90)
    - Saybrook College - Master Search, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 91)
    - Silliman College - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 92)
    - Silliman College - Dean Hill Announcement, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 93)
    - Silliamn College - Master Appointment - Christakis, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 94)
    - Silliman College - Master Resignation - Krauss, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 95)
    - Silliman College - Master Search - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 96)
    - Sterling Committee - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 97)
    - Ezra Stiles College - Associate Master Appointment - Camacho, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 98)
    - Ezra Stiles College - Master Appointment - Pitti, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 99)
    - Trumbull College - Master Appointment - Clark, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Student Organizations
    - Association of Chinese Students and Scholars at Yale - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 101)
    - European Student Conference - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 102)
    - Fossil Free Yale - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 103)
    - Fossil Free Yale -Petitions, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 104)
    - Fossil Free Yale - Petitions, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 105)
    - Glee Club - Recording Disc, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 106)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Senate - Annual Letter, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 107)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Senate - Meeting Issues, 2015 February 23 (Box 25, Folder 108)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Senate and Graduate Assembly - Meeting, 2015 April 16 (Box 25, Folder 109)
    - Junion Class Council - Biographies, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 110)
    - Students Against Sexual Violence at Yale - Meeting, 2013 August 27 (Box 25, Folder 111)
    - Student Leaders Reporting - Student Governance, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 112)
    - UC Davis Pre-Health Student Alliance - Conference, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 113)
    - Whiffenpoofs - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 114)
    - Yale African Students Association - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 25, Folder 115)
    - Yale College Council - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 116)
    - Yale College Council - Fossil Fuels and Environmental Sustainability, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 117)
    - Student Organziations - Yale College Council - Meeting with Salovey and Goff-Crews, 2014 November 14 (Box 25, Folder 118)
    - Yale Entrepreneurs and Innovators (YEI), 2014 February 25 (Box 25, Folder 119)
    - Yale Undergraduate Aerospace Association - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Subject Files
    - 43 Hillhouse Art Selections, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Access Yale - Financial Aid Statistics, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Access Yale Initiative, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Accessibility (folder 1 of 3), 2013 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Accessibility (folder 2 of 3), 2013 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Accessibility (folder 3 of 3), 2013 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Admissions - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Admissions - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Admissions - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Admissions - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Admissions - Cosmos Club - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Admissions - Dean Quinlan - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Admissions - Dean Search, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Admissions - Early Decision - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Admissions - E-Mail Correspondence, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Admissions - Meetng, 2013 September 3 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Admissions - New College, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Admissions - Requests, 2013-2014 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Admissions - Select Matriculating Students Class of 2017, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Africa Initiative, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Africa Initiative - Candidates - Adams, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Africa Initiative - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Africa Initiative - Memoranda, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Africa Initiative - Senior Women in Government - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - African Women Leadership Program - Memorandum, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Yale AIDS Memorial Project, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Yale AIDS Memorial Website, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Alcohol, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Alcohol Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Alcohol - Realist Evaluation Report, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Alcohol and Sex - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Alumni Association of the Northwest, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Assembly, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Assembly LXXIII, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Board Meeting, 2013 April 27 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Board Meeting, 2014 September 6 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Board Meeting, 2015 February 6 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Executive Director Dollhopf, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Florida Clubs, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Global Alumni Leadership Exchange (GALE), 2014 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - President's Summit, 2014 April 3 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Strategic Plan, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Central New Jersey, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Cincinnati, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Cleveland - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Georgia, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Greenwich, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of New Jersey - Reception, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of New York, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of New York - Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Palm Beach - Visit - Disc, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Pittsburgh - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Yale Club of Singapore - Reception, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Alumni - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Alumni - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Alumni - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Alumni - Correpondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Alumni - Hong Kong Alumni, Parents and Friends - Event Remarks, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Alumni - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender (LGBT) Reunion, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Alumni - Association of Yale Alumni - Plan for Connecting Alumni and Student Presentations, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Alumni - Yale Asian Alumni Reunion, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Alumni - Fellow Ballot - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Alumni - Reunion Gift Committee, 2015 April 22 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Alumni - Reunion Weekends, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Alumni - Reunions, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Alumni - Reunions - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Alumni - Reunions - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Alumni - Reunions - Class of 1954-Disc, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - Alumni - Reunions - Next 50 Years Panel, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Alumni - Senior Living - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Alumni - Wheeler - Notes, 2014 February 4 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Alumni - Yale Alumni in Energy - Conference, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - American Studies Association Boycott - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Animal Care and Use Program - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Announcements, 2013-2014 (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Announcements, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 78)
    - Announcements - Johnson Gift, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - Announcements - Johnson Gift Responses, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 80)
    - Announcements - Notes from Woodbridge Hall, 2012-2013 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Announcements - Notes from Woodbridge Hall, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Responses, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Anti - Semitism - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Appointments and Reviews, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Architecture - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Argentina - Embassy - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Arts Council of Greater New Haven - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Arts Discretionary Funds Guidelines, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Baccalaureate Address - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Bangladesh - Ex-Deputy Secretary, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Bangladesh - Ministry of Education - Corrrespondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Yale Baroque Opera - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Bilateral Forum on Higher Education, Innovation and Research - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Biomedical Devices and Instrumentation - UCONN and Yale Workshop, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Black Solidarity Conference - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Bluegrass - Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Brady-Johnson Program in Grand Strategy - Annual Report, 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Brady-Johnson Program in Grand Strategy - Annual Report, 2012-2014 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Brady-Johnson Program in Grand Strategy - Annual Report, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Brady-Johnson Program in Grand Strategy - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Brady-Johnson Program in Grand Strategy - Director Appointment - Bradley, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Brady-Johnson Program in Grand Strategy - Discussion Topic, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Brazil, 2015 January 15 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Brazil - Consulate General - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Brazil - First Lady Meeting, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Brazil - Memorandum and Overview, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Brazil - Nacion-Salovey Article, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Brazil - Yale and Brazil Profile, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Budget Update, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Burma - Daw Suu - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Campaign - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Campus and Fire Safety - Annual Report, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Campus Compact - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Capital Plan, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Carbon Charge Task Force - Correspondence and Report, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Carlisle Tragegy Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Celebrities - Bono - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Cengage Learning - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Chabad House - Dedication, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Chaplain - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Chaplain - Meeting, 2014 February 6 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Chauffeurs - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - China - All China Youth Federation - Dialogue, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - China - CCTV - Salovey in China - Disc, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - China - Central Party School - Yale Senior Government Leadership Program, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - China - Leadership Center in Beijing - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - China - Vice Minister Xinsheng - Visit, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - China - Vice Premier Yandong - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - China - Vice Premier Yandong - Meeting, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - China - Vice Premier Yandong - Proposed Law - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - China Article - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - City Works - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Class Day - Biden - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Class Day - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Class of 2018 - Crib Sheet, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Climate Change - Correspondence, 2012-2014 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Yale Untimate Summit - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Collaborative Commons - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - College Pipeline Initiative, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Commencement - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Commencement - Program, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Commencement - Timeline of Events, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Commencement Ceremony - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Commencement Weekend, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Commons - Woolsey Hall Renovations, Events and Budget, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Communications, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - Community Colleges - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Compensation - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Connecticut Hospice, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - Connecticut Women's Hall of Fame - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Campus and New Haven Statistics, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Cultural Centers - Correspondence and Report, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Yale Dance Theater - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - Decanal Structure - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - Deceased List, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 76)
    - Defense Science Study Group - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - Democratic National Committee, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Digital Yale - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - Disability Issues - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 80)
    - Diversity - Achieving and Maintaining in Yale College, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 81)
    - Diversity - Faculty Report, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 82)
    - Diversity Summit - Lunch - Notes, 2014 February 12 (Box 27, Folder 83)
    - Diversity - Promoting Diversity and Equal Opportunity at Yale, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 84)
    - Diversity Summit II - February (folder 1 of 2), 2014 (Box 27, Folder 85)
    - Diversity Summit II - February (folder 2 of 2), 2014 (Box 27, Folder 86)
    - Diversity Summit - Report, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 87)
    - Divestment - Fossil Fuel - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 88)
    - Dwight Hall, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 89)
    - Eagle Scouts - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 90)
    - Earthquake Relief - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 91)
    - Ebola - Announcement, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 92)
    - Ecuador - Ambassador Cely - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 93)
    - Ecuador - President Carea - Visit, 2014 April 7 (Box 27, Folder 94)
    - Education - Studies - Budget and Summary 2015 (Box 27, Folder 95)
    - Education - Programs and Partnerships for New Haven Youth, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 96)
    - Egypt - Gabr - Meeting, 2015 March 14 (Box 27, Folder 97)
    - Elihu Club - Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 27, Folder 98)
    - Emotional Intelligence - Correspondence, Undated (Box 27, Folder 99)
    - Emotional Intelligence - Development Notes, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 100)
    - Emotional Intelligence - Santander Presentation, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 101)
    - Emotional Intelligence in China, Undated (Box 27, Folder 102)
    - Energy Conservation - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 103)
    - Enterprise Risk Management, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 104)
    - Entrepreneurship- Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 105)
    - Environment - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 106)
    - Yale Environment Sustainability Summit - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 107)
    - Episcopal Church at Yale - Shipman Controversy, 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 108)
    - European Student Conference - Report, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - European Union - Ambassador Kannard, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Federal Relations - Budget and Analysis, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Faxon Law New Haven Road Race - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Financial Aid - Access Yale - Publication and Review, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Financial Aid - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Fire Evacuation Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Yale Forum for Strategic Impact - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Fossil Fuels - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Dick Foster Project - Yale Health Collaborative, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Founder's Day, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Franke Program in Science and the Humanities - Director Appointment - Prum, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Fraternities - Phi Beta Kappa, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Free Speech - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Freedom of Expression - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Freshman Assembly, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Freshman Scholars at Yale Program, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Henry Louis Gates, Jr. Lecture - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Gender Roles Symposium - Yale Women and Women Faculty Forum, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Germany - Ambassador Ammon - Meeting, 2013 January 15 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Ghana - Presient Mahama - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Global and Strategic Initiatives - Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Global Constitutionalism Seminar, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Global Health Initiative, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Goals and Priorities - President, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Gourmet Heaven - Issues, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Grading -Charts, Undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Housing, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Graduate Student Life - Issues and Initiatives - Talking Points, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Grafitti - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Grant and Contract Financial Administration Report, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Hall of Graduate Studies - Correspondence and Petition, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Halloween Invitations, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Handsome Dan - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Harkness Tower, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Health Care, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - High Value Detainee Interregation Group, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Holiday Party, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2014-2015 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Hopkins School Article on Salovey, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Housing, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Elm Street Graduate Housing, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Howland Lecturer - Prince of Wales Invitation, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Ariana Huffington - Publication, Undated (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - "I Have a Dream" Proposed Installation (folder 1 of 2), 2013 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - "I Have a Dream" Proposed Installation (folder 2 of 2), 2013 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Immigration Reform - Statement, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Inauguration, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Inauguration - Invites and RSVPs, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Inauguration - Presidential Inauguration Committee, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Inauguration - Procession, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Inauguration - Staff Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Inauguration - Symposia, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - India - Sustainable Development Summit - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 56)
    - India - US and India Energy Partnership Summit, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 57)
    - India Initiative, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 58)
    - India Initiative and South Asia Council - Shivi Notes, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 59)
    - Information Technology Services, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 60)
    - Information Technology Services - Improvement, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 61)
    - Information Technology Services - Notes, 2012 (Box 28, Folder 62)
    - Information Technology Services - Project Portfolio Preservation, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 63)
    - Institutional Animal Care and Use - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 64)
    - Institutional Review Board's Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 65)
    - Intellectual Property Policy - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 66)
    - International Affairs Office - Meeting, 2013 January 16 (Box 28, Folder 67)
    - International Families Luncheon, 2013 August 22 (Box 28, Folder 68)
    - International Festival of Arts and Ideas, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 69)
    - International Parents Luncheon, 2014 August 21 (Box 28, Folder 70)
    - International Rescue Committee - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 71)
    - Internationalization - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 72)
    - Internationalization - Panel Notes, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 73)
    - Interviews - Themes, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 74)
    - Israel - Ambassador Dermer - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 75)
    - Japan - Ambassador - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 76)
    - Japan Consulate - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 77)
    - Jewish Advocate - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 78)
    - Jewish Federation of Greater New Haven, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 79)
    - Journalism Initiative - Brill - Notes, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 80)
    - Karmapa, Ogyen Trinley Dorje - Meeting, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 81)
    - Kentucky Colonel - Ephemera, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 82)
    - Martin Luther King Day - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 83)
    - Kissinger Lunch Honoring Yandmg, 2013 November 22 (Box 28, Folder 84)
    - Kissinger Meeting, 2013 December 17 (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Kissinger Book Discussion, 2014 September 19 (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Latino and African - American High School Internship Program, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 87)
    - Leadership Council - Packet, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transexual and Queer Spring Social, 2015 March 27 (Box 28, Folder 89)